BU Records: Office of the President (Abner Vernon McCall), Inclusive: 1845-1981, undated, Bulk: 1961-1981
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
BU Records: Office of the President (Abner Vernon McCall)
Inclusive: 1845-1981, undated, Bulk: 1961-1981
Baylor University, The Texas Collection http://www.baylor.edu/lib/texas/
BU/141
McCall, Abner Vernon, 1915 -
249 document boxes and 2 oversized boxes.
BU Records: Office of the President (Abner Vernon McCall) contains the presidential records of Baylor University's 10th president, Abner Vernon McCall who served from 1961-1981. The records contain correspondence and documents related to the internal workings of the university as well as external organizations McCall and Baylor had ties to during his time as Baylor's president.
Administrative Information
Physical Description
General condition: Average.
Biography/Profile
Abner Vernon McCall was born on 1915 June 9 in Perrin, Texas, to parents Gertrude Elizabeth Rhoades McCall and Harry Vernon McCall. At the age of 3, McCall’s father passed away from the flu. After his death, his mother was unable to care for McCall and his siblings and they were placed in the Masonic School and Home in Fort Worth, Texas. Although not much is known about Abner’s early life at this school, it is well known that Abner flourished academically. Graduating as the Valedictorian of his class, Abner earned the prestigious Masonic Scholarship, providing him the funding to attend Baylor University. Continuing his successes at Baylor, McCall graduated as valedictorian of the Baylor Law Class of 1938.
Entering law practice, McCall remained near Baylor to teach law classes, serving as an assistant professor from 1938 to 1942. He left Baylor for a year to earn a Masters of Law at the University of Michigan. After receiving his degree, he worked with the Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) for three years before returning to Baylor. Two years after his return, he was appointed Dean of the Law School. During his time teaching, he also was appointed a Texas Supreme Court Justice in 1956 June by then Governor Allan Shivers.
By 1959, McCall was appointed Executive Vice President of Baylor University. In 1961, McCall was appointed President of Baylor University, a position he held for 21 years. During his tenure at Baylor, he was instrumental in expanding Baylor’s campus, raising the enrollment numbers, and improving the financial conditions of the university. While McCall was president, he continued to teach law courses. In 1981, McCall became the Chancellor of Baylor. He served in this capacity until 1985, then served as President Emeritus.
McCall was known for his traditional Baptist views on social issues pertaining to campus life, including dancing, alcohol, and card playing. He served in many religious organizations in a variety of capacities, including President of the Baptist General Convention of Texas in 1964-1965 and Vice President of the Southern Baptist Convention in 1979-1980. Growing up surrounded by Masons, McCall was also involved in the Masonic Order and was coronated a 33rd degree Scottish Rite Mason in 1969. In 1991, McCall was honored with the Grand Cross, the highest honor granted to a Free Mason.
McCall passed away at the age of 90 on 1995 June 11 and is buried in Oakwood Cemetery in Waco, Texas.
Scope and Content
This collection begins in 1845 and ends in 1981, with some items undated. While this collection mainly encompasses files from Abner McCall's presidency at Baylor University from 1961 to 1981, it also includes McCall's files from 1959-1961 when he served as Executive Vice President.
Series I. Board of Trustees includes meeting minutes and correspondence from the various boards that existed while McCall was president, which ultimately consolidated into one board by the end of his presidency. Series II. Internal includes correspondence, reports, and other materials that were produced specifically for Baylor University. This includes departments, organizations, and correspondence topically related to events or issues at Baylor. Series III. External includes correspondence, reports, newsletters, and other materials that were produced outside of Baylor or for institutions outside of Baylor. This includes organizations such as the Baptist General Convention, Christian Life Commission, Texas System of Natural Laboratories, and many others. Some of these materials are related to McCall and his involvement in external organizations and issues while others deal specifically with his presidency at Baylor. Series IV. People includes mostly correspondence but also other documents that were organized and filed by a person's last name. Series V. Personal includes any personal files kept with McCall's presidential files, correspondence relating to engagements McCall was invited to while president, and telegrams sent and received.
Series II. Internal, Series III. External, and Series IV. People are the largest series in the collection. Throughout the entire collection, there are cross reference sheets within folders and as separate folders that direct researchers to other files with similar topics. These cross reference sheets were created and filed by McCall's assistants during his presidency and retained during processing. All files dated to 1981 only include his last five months as president. BU Records: Chancellor's Office (Abner Vernon McCall) contains the remaining seven months of 1981.
Arrangement
Prior to current processing, this collection was housed in labeled folders in relative chronological order and alphabetical thereafter. There were miscellaneous folders for each year and every letter of the alphabet. With the exception of these folders, original titles were retained where possible and any title information added during processing is noted in brackets in the folder titles.
Currently, the collection is organized in five series: I. Board of Trustees, II. Internal, III. External, IV. People, V. Personal. Within all five series, folders are arranged relatively alphabetically and chronological thereafter.
Access Restrictions
All requests for copying of materials must be submitted to The Texas Collection in writing. Please use the Request Form for Copying Materials sheet. Unpublished materials authored or otherwise produced by the creator (s) of this collection are in the public domain. There are no restrictions on use. Copyright status for other collection materials is unknown. Transmission or reproduction of materials protected by U.S. Copyright Law (Title 17, U.S.C.) beyond that allowed by fair use requires the written permission of the copyright owners. Works not in the public domain cannot be commercially exploited without permission of the copyright owners. Responsibility for any use rests exclusively with the user.
Acquisition Information
Accession No. BU/141. Acquired 1974-06-13
Related Resources
Items in related collections
BU Records: Chancellor's Office (Abner Vernon McCall), Inclusive: 1980-1988, undated, Bulk: 1981-1985
BU Records: President Emeritus' Office (Abner Vernon McCall), Inclusive: 1857-1995, undated, Bulk: 1985-1995
Abner Vernon McCall papers
BU Records: Abner Vernon McCall Tribute
BU Records: Office of the President, Chancellor and President Emeritus: William Richardson White, Inclusive: 1936-1977, undated, Bulk: 1950-1969, undated
BU Records: President's Office: Herbert Hal Reynolds
Related references
“Abner Vernon McCall (1915-1995).”Abner Vernon McCall, The University of Texas at Austin. Accessed 2019 December 1.
Find A Grave, Inc. "Abner Vernon McCall." Memorial #15715101. Databases. Accessed 2019 December 1.
Saxon, Wolfgang. “Abner V. McCall, 80, Educator Who Led in Expansion of Baylor.” The New York Times, 1995 June 12.
Index Terms
Subjects (Persons)
McCall, Abner, 1915-
Subjects (Organizations)
Baylor University -- Administration.; Baylor University -- Campus.; Baylor University -- History -- 20th century.; Baylor University -- Presidents -- Archives.; Baylor University -- Records and correspondence.; Baylor University. Office of the President -- Records and correspondence.
Subjects
Baptist universities and colleges -- Texas -- Waco.; Baylor University -- Buildings.; Correspondence.; Minutes (Records); Newsletters.; Records (Documents); Speeches.
- Board of Trustees, 1958-1981, undated; 1
  Administrative Information
  Physical Description
  General condition: Average.
  Biography/Profile
  This series includes meeting minutes from the various Baylor Board of Trustees, as well as correspondence and other related materials. During McCall's presidency, the Board of Trustees underwent several changes. The Board of Trustees included 48 members elected by the Baptist General Convention of Texas. These members were divided between three boards: a Houston board responsible for the Baylor College of Medicine, a Dallas board responsible for the Baylor Medical Center, College of Dentistry, and School of Nursing, and a Waco board responsible for the main Baylor campus. All three boards met together twice a year as the "General Board."
  In 1968, the trustees voted to create a separate corporation with a separate board to handle the affairs of the College of Medicine in Houston, thereby replacing the need for the Houston board. The College of Dentistry underwent a similar process in 1971, but it is unclear when the Dallas board officially dissolved. At some point in 1971, the General Board became known simply as the Board of Trustees and met bimonthly. This series is in average condition.
  - Board of Trustees: Dallas Executive Committee Meetings, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees: Dallas Executive Committee Meetings, 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees: Dallas Executive Committee Meetings, 1964-1966 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees: Dallas Executive Committee Meetings, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees: Houston Executive Committee Meetings, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees: Houston Executive Committee Meetings, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees: Houston Executive Committee Meetings, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees: Houston Executive Committee Meetings, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Board of Trustees: Houston Executive Committee Meetings (1 of 2), 1963 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Board of Trustees: Houston Executive Committee Meetings (2 of 2), 1963 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees: Houston Executive Committee Meetings, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees: Houston Executive Committee Meetings, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees: Houston Executive Committee Meetings, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees: Houston Executive Committee Meetings, 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees: Baylor College of Medicine, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees: Baylor College of Medicine, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees: Baylor College of Medicine (1 of 2), 1972 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Board of Trustees: Baylor College of Medicine (2 of 2), 1972 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Board of Trustees: Baylor College of Medicine, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees: Baylor College of Medicine (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees: Baylor College of Medicine (2 of 2), 1974 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees: Baylor College of Medicine, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees: Baylor College of Medicine (1 of 2), 1976 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees: Baylor College of Medicine (2 of 2), 1976 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees: Baylor College of Medicine (1 of 2), 1977 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees: Baylor College of Medicine (2 of 2), 1977 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Board of Trustees: Baylor College of Medicine, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Board of Trustees: Baylor College of Medicine, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees: Waco Executive Committee Meetings, 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees: Waco Executive Committee Meetings, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees: Waco Executive Committee Meetings, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees: Waco Executive Committee Meetings, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees: Waco Board Meetings (1 of 3), 1964 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees: Waco Board Meetings (2 of 3), 1964 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees: Waco Board Meetings (3 of 3), 1964 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Board of Trustees: Waco Board Meetings (1 of 3), 1965 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees: Waco Board Meetings (2 of 3), 1965 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees: Waco Board Meetings (3 of 3), 1965 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees: Waco Board Meetings (1 of 2), 1966 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees: Waco Board Meetings (2 of 2), 1966 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees: Waco Board Meetings (1 of 2), 1967 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees: Waco Board Meetings (2 of 2), 1967 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees: Waco Board Meetings, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Board of Trustees: Waco Board Meetings, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Board of Trustees: Waco Board Meetings (1 of 2), 1970 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees: Waco Board Meetings (2 of 2), 1970 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees: General Meetings, 1960-1961 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees: General Meetings (1 of 2), 1962 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees: General Meetings (2 of 2), 1962 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees: General Meetings, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees: General Meetings (1 of 2), 1964 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees: General Meetings (2 of 2), 1964 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Board of Trustees: General Meetings, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees: General Meetings, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees: General Meetings, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees: General Meetings (1 of 2), 1968 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees: General Meetings (2 of 2), 1968 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees: General Meetings, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees: General Meetings, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees: General Meetings, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Board of Trustees Meetings, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Board of Trustees Working File, 1979-1981 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Chairman of the Board (Dewey Presley), 1975-1981 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Committees (Trustees), 1974-1979 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence (Board of Trustees), 1961-1970, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Resolutions, 1969, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Trustee Biographies (A-L), 1967-1972 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Trustee Biographies (M-Z), 1967-1972 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Trustee Biographical Material (Permanent) (1 of 2), 1975-1980 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Trustee Biographical Material (Permanent) (2 of 2), 1975-1980 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Trustee Correspondence, 1972-1975 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Trustee Correspondence, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Trustee Correspondence, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Trustee Correspondence, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Trustee Correspondence (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Trustee Correspondence (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Trustee Correspondence (1 of 2), 1980 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Trustee Correspondence (2 of 2), 1980 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Trustee Lists, 1958-1965 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Trustee Lists, 1966-1974 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Trustee Lists, 1975-1981 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Trustees: Related Correspondence and Files, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Trustees: Related Correspondence and Files, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Trustees: Related Correspondence and Files, 1961-1964 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Trustees: Related Correspondence and Files, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Trustees: Related Correspondence and Files (1 of 2), 1967 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Trustees: Related Correspondence and Files (2 of 2), 1967 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Trustees: Related Correspondence and Files, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Trustees: Related Correspondence and Files (1 of 2), 1969 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Trustees: Related Correspondence and Files (2 of 2), 1969 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Trustees: Related Correspondence and Files, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Trustees: Related Correspondence and Files, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Trustees: Related Correspondence and Files, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Trustees: Related Correspondence and Files, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Trustee Reports and Correspondence for General Board Meeting, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Internal, 1845-1981, undated; 2
  This series includes correspondence, reports, minutes, and other materials relating to the inner-workings of Baylor. Materials produced specifically for Baylor or by Baylor departments, organizations, and individuals can be found in this series. Some files are restricted due to the existence of personally identifiable information, or based on the current restriction policy governing university archives. This series is in average condition.
  Access Restrictions
  Some folders within this series are restricted due to personally identifiable information, confidentiality, and current laws and policies. These folders are denoted as restricted. Contact an archivist for details.
  - A Cross-Reference Sheets, 1966-1977 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Academic Affairs, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Academic Appeals [RESTRICTED], 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Academic Department Memos, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Academic Freedom, 1964-1972 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Academic Reform, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Academic and Non-Academic Calendar, 1975-1981 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Academics: Final Report of Special Committee Appointed to Inquire into Academic Aspects of Baylor University, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Academy of Health Sciences, 1972-1981 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - A Capella Choir, 1960-1964 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Accounting Department, 1965-1974 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Administrative Authority, Policies, and Procedures, 1969-1973 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Administrative Vice-President, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Admissions and Registrar [RESTRICTED], 1963-1968 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Admissions and Registrar [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Admissions and Registrar [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Admissions and Registrar [RESTRICTED], 1971-1972 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Admissions and Registrar [RESTRICTED], 1973 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Admissions and Registrar [RESTRICTED], 1974 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Admissions and Registrar (1 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Admissions and Registrar (2 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Admissions and Registrar (1 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Admissions and Registrar (2 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Admissions and Registrar (1 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Admissions and Registrar (2 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Admissions and Registrar (1 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Admissions and Registrar (2 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Admissions and Registrar (1 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Admissions and Registrar (2 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Admissions and Registrar (1 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Admissions and Registrar (2 of 2) [RESTRICTED], 1980 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Admissions and Registrar [RESTRICTED], 1981 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Agreements, 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Air Force Reserve Officer Training Corps (AFROTC), 1974-1981 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Alpha Chi, 1971-1977 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Alpha Epsilon Delta, 1969-1979 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Alpha Kappa Psi, 1964-1965 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Alpha Phi Omega (APO), 1959-1965 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Alumni/Ex-Students Association, 1959-1960 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Alumni/Ex-Students Association, 1961-1965 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Alumni/Ex-Students Association, 1966-1968 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Alumni/Ex-Students Association, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Alumni/Ex-Students Association: Operation Second Century, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Alumni/Ex-Students Association, 1970-1971 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Alumni/Ex-Students Association, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Alumni/Ex-Students Association, 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Alumni/Ex-Students Association, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Alumni/Ex-Students Association, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Alumni/Ex-Students Association, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Alumni/Ed-Students Association, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Alumni/Ed-Students Association, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Alumni Fund Raising, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Loyalty Fund, 1959-1962 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Angel Flight, 1975-1977 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Anniversary (125th), 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Armstrong Browning Library, 1959-1981 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Art Department, 1962-1974 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Articles of Incorporation, 1963-1969 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Arts Festival and Exhibits, 1960-1977 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Assistant Vice President and Budget Director, 1975-1981 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Assistant Vice President and Business Manager, 1976-1980 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Assistant Vice President and Controller, 1976-1980 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Assistant Vice President and Director of Student Financial Aid [RESTRICTED], 1967-1981 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Associate Dean of Faculties and Graduate Dean, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Associate Dean of Students, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Athenean Club, 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Athletic Advisers, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Athletic Council, 1969-1971 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Athletic Department, 1959-1961 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Athletic Department, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Athletic Department, 1962-1963 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Athletic Department, 1964-1965 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Athletic Department, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Athletic Department, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Athletic Department — Anti-Bridges (1 of 2), 1967 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Athletic Department — Anti-Bridges (2 of 2), 1967 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Athletic Department — For J. Bridges (1 of 2), 1967 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Athletic Department — For J. Bridges (2 of 2), 1967 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Athletic Department (1 of 2), 1968 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Athletic Department (2 of 2), 1968 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Athletic Department, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Athletic Department, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Athletic Department, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Athletic Department, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Athletic Department, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Athletic Department, 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Athletic Department, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Athletic Department (1 of 2), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Athletic Department (2 of 2), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Athletic Department (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Athletic Department (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Athletic Department (1 of 3), 1980 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Athletic Department (2 of 3), 1980 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Athletic Department (3 of 3), 1980 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Athletic Department, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Athletic Facility, 1977-1980 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Attendance Records, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 8)